import { QuestionType } from "@/components/question/multipleChoice";
export const fractionsQuestion1Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "Simplify the following expression: 3/4 + 2/5",
  options: ["23/20", "29/20", "15/20", "7/10"],
  answer: "23/20",
};

export const fractionsQuestion2Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "Subtract 5/8 from 7/8",
  options: ["4/8", "1/4", "3/8", "1/8"],
  answer: "1/4",
};

export const fractionsQuestion3Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "Multiply 3/5 by 4/7",
  options: ["12/35", "7/20", "15/35", "10/21"],
  answer: "12/35",
};

export const fractionsQuestion4Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "Convert the mixed fraction 3 2/3 to an improper fraction.",
  options: ["11/3", "9/3", "10/3", "8/3"],
  answer: "11/3",
};

export const fractionsQuestion5Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "Convert 11/3 to a mixed fraction.",
  options: ["3 2/3", "3 1/3", "2 2/3", "4 2/3"],
  answer: "3 2/3",
};

export const dividingFractionQuestion1Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "Divide 4/5 by 2",
  options: ["2/5", "4/10", "5/8", "4/3"],
  answer: "2/5",
};

export const dividingFractionQuestion2Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "Divide 7/8 by 3",
  options: ["7/24", "21/8", "3/7", "8/21"],
  answer: "7/24",
};

export const dividingFractionQuestion3Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "Divide 5/6 by 4",
  options: ["5/24", "6/20", "1/4", "5/12"],
  answer: "5/24",
};

export const dividingFractionQuestion4Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "Divide 9/10 by 3",
  options: ["9/30", "3/10", "1/3", "27/10"],
  answer: "3/10",
};

export const dividingWholeFractionQuestion1Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "Divide 4 by 1/2",
  options: ["2", "8", "6", "4"],
  answer: "8",
};

export const dividingWholeFractionQuestion2Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "Divide 6 by 3/4",
  options: ["8", "10", "7.5", "4.5"],
  answer: "8",
};

export const dividingWholeFractionQuestion3Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "Divide 3/5 by 2/3",
  options: ["9/10", "6/15", "5/9", "3/10"],
  answer: "9/10",
};

export const dividingWholeFractionQuestion4Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "Divide 4/7 by 2/5",
  options: ["8/35", "10/14", "20/14", "10/7"],
  answer: "10/7",
};
